## Ivan Ravić

Software Engineer



- k https://www.ivanravic.com/
- nttps://github.com/IvanRavic88
- in linkedin.com/in/ivan-ravić-b3aa36143
- Lazarevac, Serbia
- +381655254013

### **Profile**

System Administrator with a Master's in Electrical and Computer Engineering, recently certified as an AWS Developer - Associate. Gaining experience with cloud computing, automation, and infrastructure as code using tools like Terraform, Ansible, Docker, and AWS services. Familiar with CI/CD pipelines and configuration management, with a solid foundation in web development using NextJS, Typescript, Python, and Flask. Excited to apply my growing DevOps skills and technical expertise in a challenging environment. Explore my projects and experience on my GitHub profile and portfolio at ivanravic.com.

### **Education**

College of Applied Studies The School of Electrical and Computer Engineering of Applied Studies Master studies (appl.)

2017 - 2019 | Belgrade, Serbia

## Skills

#### DevOps

Ansible, Terraform and GitHub Actions

#### **NextJS**

Typescript and Javascript CSS

## Tailwind Python

Flask and Jinja

## **Professional Experience**

#### **System Administrator**

EPS, Kolubara

2022 - present

Network and servers maintenance of the CQMS system

#### **CQMS** engineer

EPS, Kolubara

2021 - 2022

Network and servers maintenance of the CQMS system

#### Electrical engineer

EPS, Kolubara

2017 - 2021

Responsible for automatic controled systems

#### Electrician in group for conveyer belts

EPS, Kolubara

2015 - 2017

Maintenance

### Courses

**100 Days of Code - The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp by Dr. Angela Yu** *Udemy.com* 

# Complete Web Development Bootcamp by Dr. Angela Yu

Udemy.com

## Understanding TypeScript by Maximilian Schwarzmüller

Udemy.com

## Certification

# **AWS Certified Developer - Associate** (DVA-C02)

AWS training and certification

